# ATHARVA

VERMA

#### CONTACT



**100-730-5528** 



thehammerrrguy@gmail.com



A-901 Akash Enclave, Lucknow



www.thehammerguy.com

#### **SKILLS**

- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Verbal & Written communication
- Electronics
- Computer Hardware & Software
- Visual Basics/Java Script/Python/html
- Drone schematics

## **LANGUAGE**

English .....

Japanese

Hindi •••••

# **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

- School Band (Lead singer)
- Organizing multiple events in the institution.
- Won multiple art competitions.

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I have a clear, logical mind with a practical approach to problemsolving and a drive to see things through to completion. I have more than 4 years of experience multiple sectors. I am eager to learn, I enjoy overcoming challenges, and I have a genuine interest in learning new ways of making organisations successful.

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelors in Mechanical Engineering(B.Tech)

NIET Greater Nopida (2019 -

- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing (Google)
- 3D Printing (NIET)

#### Intermediate Education

City Montessory school 2017

The Chopras (TC Global) - (2018)

SAT score - 1280 **IELTS** score - 7.6

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Nvidia (Gamerconnect)**

Operations Manager (July 2019 - Aug 2020)

• Organized multiple events with the assigned team for the public and PC enthusiasts to experience the latest hardware.

## BattleAx (JMD Group)

Digital Marketing Manager (May 2018 - Oct 2018)

• Lead the marketing team in growing the companie's overall sales.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Ranjee's Hotel

Digital Marketing Manager (May 2018 - Oct 2018)

• Lead the marketing team in growing the companie's overall sales .

# Atharvika Ecreations PVT. LTD.

Digital Marketing Manager (May 2019 - June 2019)

• Lead the marketing team in growing the companie's overall sales .

# B. Sons Mfg. & Trade Co.

Machinery Maintenance and R&d Manager (Sept 2020 - June 2022)

• Lead the machinery team to the better maintenance of the machinery and R&d on new textile machines )